

MICHAEL D. CHAPMAN

My name is Michael Chapman and I am a highly skilled Front-end Web Developer and Graphic Designer with a tireless work ethic and humble attitude. I have extensive professional experience in web development, marketing, branding, product development, and print design. I am very versatile and a resourceful problem solver who is adept at the creation process. I'm also well organized, a great leader who has proven the ability to manage multiple projects simultaneously.

Location: San Diego, Ca. Cell: 760-310-3017

Email: furthermorepro@gmail.com Website: michaeldchapman.com

SKILLS

Web Development

UX Design

Marketing

Branding

Product Development

Print Design

PROGRAMS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

Shopify

MailChimp

DocuSign

InDesign

Photoshop

Illustrator

Excel

Word

STUDYING

Figma Webflow Solidity

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science

The Art Institute of California 2006 - 2009

AWARDS

Student Achievement Award

College Graduation Art Institute of California

Peoples Choice Award

Fine Art Show

Juried Biennial - Carlsbad, Ca.

Honorable Mention

Fine Art Show Juried Biennial - Vista, Ca.

INTERESTS

Technology

Design

Blockchain

Community Building

Engineering

Fine Art

Skateboarding

Off-roading

Gardening

WORK EXPERIENCE

Independent Trading Co.

Creative Director January 2017 to Present

- Developed & Managed B2C/B2B Websites
- Designed & Managed Marketing
- Designed Company & Product Branding
- · Designed Sales Assets
- · Designed Printed Media
- · Designed Tech Pack Templates
- Designed DocuSign Templates
- · Developed Soft Goods
- · Communicated with Overseas Factories

Riviera Paddlesurf

Designer / Product Developer November 2013 - January 2017

- Developed & Managed Website
- Designed & Managed Marketing
- · Designed Product Branding
- · Designed Sales Assets
- Designed Printed Media
- Designed Tech Pack Templates
- · Developed Hard Goods
- Communicated with Overseas Factories

Dye Precision / Pro-Tec

Interactive Media Designer February 2013 - August 2013

- · Designed Assets for Websites
- Designed Assets for Live Broadcasts
- · Created Printed Media

Rayzist Photomask Inc.

Senior Web & Graphic Designer March 2010 - February 2013

- Developed & Managed Websites
- · Designed & Managed Marketing
- · Designed Product Branding